[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1972 horror film, directed by Bob Clark, was shot in 14 days and centers around a theater troupe.", "correct_answer": "Children Shouldnt Play with Dead Things", "incorrect_answers": ["The House by the Cemetery", "Deathdream", "Escape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The people of which country watched the most TV per week in 2005?", "correct_answer": "Thailand", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philippines", "The USA", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Until what age can the female elephant (called a cow) produce offspring?", "correct_answer": "50 years", "incorrect_answers": ["15 years", "75 years", "7 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Roswell UFO incident involves the discovery of debris of an alleged extraterrestrial space ship, which had crashed into a field near Roswell, New Mexico, USA. In which year did this happen?", "correct_answer": "1947", "incorrect_answers": ["1956", "1973", "1968"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term describes the concentration of a solution in moles per liter?", "correct_answer": "molarity", "incorrect_answers": ["osmosis", "diffusion", "molality"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the characters from the 1939 movie The Wizard of Oz says the phrase Theres no place like home?", "correct_answer": "Dorothy", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cowardly Lion", "The Scarecrow", "The Tin Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dome of Hagia Sophia in Istanbul (former Constantinople) is supported by how many massive piers?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "2", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a popular Greek legend, Thessalonike, the sister of this historical figure, was transformed into a mermaid after her death.", "correct_answer": "Alexander the Great", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristotle", "Helen of Troy", "Orpheus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not true about the bird eggshell?", "correct_answer": "The eggshell does not contain protein.", "incorrect_answers": ["The normal bird eggshell is porous.", "The eggshell consists of roughly 95% calcium carbonate crystals.", "The bird eggshell is covered by a structure called cuticle."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the kind of rice you should use for your risotto.", "correct_answer": "Round or semi-round rice", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown rice", "Chinese rice", "Long grained rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film style, generally used by film-makers with low budgets, originated in Denmark.", "correct_answer": "Dogma", "incorrect_answers": ["Comedy", "Surrealism", "Film Noir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How deep can a bottlenose dolphin dive?", "correct_answer": "300 meters", "incorrect_answers": ["800 meters", "1250 meters", "700 meters"]}]